Ahmet OZKESEK

GFF 17 Stonor Road W14 8RZ LONDON

M: 0772 922 3112

E: aozkesek@gmail.com

Profile

I am 25+ years experienced Software Developer/Programmer with a Bachelor of Technology in Computer Sciences Engineering. I planned, designed and developed various software for Contact Centre, ATM Management, Document Management and Workflow Management . I worked 16 years in Banking and Financial sector in Istanbul-Turkey. Now, I am seeking a Software Developer role in London where I can continue to improve myself in English.

Key Skills

Programming Languages: Java, C#, C, JavaScript

Databases: Oracle, MS-SQL, PostgreSQL

TDD: Junit, TestNG, Selenium

Tools: Gradle, Maven, Git, Docker

Frameworks: Spring, Spring Web, Spring Boot, Hibernate ORM, JSF & Primefaces, Apache Struts, ASP.NET, Entity Framework, PostSharp, JTAPI & Cisco, Genesys CTI &

IVR

Career History

Oct 2016 - date Istanbul - London Freelancer
--

- Designing and developing an Android Video Chat Application for Language Learning while Role Playing https://github.com/aozkesek/p2p-cast
- Designed and developed a Hospital Management Software with Biometric Verification for ZieZix360 from Nigeria. It was a Proof of Concept application that contains a Fingerprint and a Camera reader service module, multiple web service modules, and a web UI module. https://github.com/aozkesek/ziezix360-hm https://ziezix360.com/about-us/
- Developed some application for improving in Java, TDD <u>https://github.com/aozkesek/alev-e-commerce</u> https://github.com/aozkesek/selenium-json-suite-runner

Jul 2014 - Aug 2016	NETAS, Istanbul	Consultant
---------------------	-----------------	------------

- Designed and wrote Technical Design Document to submit a proposal for companies used Cisco Unified Communication and IP Desktop Phones.
- Created a prototype of IP Phone Service to join AVAYA Developer Connect Program

https://www.devconnectprogram.com/site/global/program_benefits/overview/index.gsp

https://downloads.avaya.com/css/P8/documents/101026461

_

- Developed an IIS Management web application for Cisco IP Phone Service https://github.com/aozkesek/iis-app-manager
 https://github.com/aozkesek/license-manager
 https://github.com/aozkesek/l
- Trained the junior team members

Nov 2001 - Jan 2014	Yapi Kredi Bank, Istanbul	Senior Programmer
---------------------	---------------------------	-------------------

- Led a Workflow Management Development team for 3 months
- Developed and maintained workflow and document management service
- Developed and maintained automatic teller machine service
- Involved upgrading of contact centre infrastructure and hardware
- Developed and maintained on-line and telephone banking service

Aug 1999 - Aug 2001	Demirbank, Istanbul	Programmer
---------------------	---------------------	------------

Developed and maintained on-line and telephone banking service

Qualifications

- Genesys, Istanbul, 2010: IP IVR Development Course
- Cisco, Istanbul, 2007: Cisco Unified Communication Manager Course
- Yapi Kredi Bank, Istanbul, 2005: Java Server Pages, MVC Apache Struts Course
- Genesys, San Fransisco, 2001: Genesys Certified Developer
- Netron, Istanbul, 1999: Internet Information Server (IIS), Active Server Page (ASP), Component Object Model (COM) Course

Education

University of Istanbul, 1990 – 1997, Bachelor of Technology in Computer Sciences Engineering (http://bilgisayar.muhendislik.istanbulc.edu.tr)

-